<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BVM Alumni</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_register">Sign in</string>

    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password (optional)</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_email">This email address is invalid</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password">This password is too short</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">This password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>
    <string name="permission_rationale">"Contacts permissions are needed for providing email completions."</string>

    <string name="PleaseWait">Please Wait...</string>
    <string name="WorkInProgress">Work is in progress</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">Main2Activity</string>

    <string name="startingDays">\u25CF The infrastructure of the college was generously designed for three year degree programme with an intake of 150 students every year.
        \n\u25CF The main building (now known as A Block) had class rooms and laboratories.
        \n\u25CF Workshops and heat engine laboratory, drawing hall, hydraulics laboratory and boiler house were separately constructed.
        \n\u25CF Shri Gordhanbhai I Patel of M/s Gordhandas Desai &amp; Co was authorized to proceed to Europe and UK to purchase equipment for workshops, laboratories and surveying.
        \n\u25CF The college thus started with the best of the equipment.</string>

    <string name="outStanding">\u25CF A spacious hall on the south end of the ground floor of the main building which at one time housed the college library was converted in 1989 into a modern – Auditorium with a capacity of 350 seats and complete with acoustical treatment, light, sound and projection facilities.
        \n\u25CF The Auditorium is beautifully carpeted and curtained and is rated today\'s as one of the best Auditorium on Vallabh Vidyanagar campus.
        \n\u25CF The Mechanical Engineering building has a Conference Room installed with complete audio-visual facilities for a capacity of 40 seats.
        \n\u25CF The college workshop was reorganized to establish laboratories for the Production Engineering programme and to house new and sophisticated machines.
        \n\u25CF On south side of the workshop a new building has come up for Civil &amp; Production Engineering Laboratories.
        \nThe building is constructed at a cost of Rs. 40 lakhs.
        \n\u25CF Principal S B Junnarkar Guest House has a facility of well furnished 10 guest rooms at the second floor of newly constructed Building is constructed with the estimated cost of Rs.60 lakhs is added to BVM infrastructure.
        \n\u25CF A Multipurpose Hall with donation from L&amp;T(with the help of CEO Er. Anil Nayak a BVMite) is also an addition to the services of alma mater.
        \n\u25CF Computer Centers of Civil, Structural, Mathematics and Mechanical Engineering are also available for students and faculties with internet connectivity.
        \n\u25CF College Canteen and conference room near Principal\'s office have been face lifted during 2006.</string>
</resources>
